[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In which movies do you hear the famous line, A martini, shaken, not stirred?", "correct_answer": "James Bond movies", "incorrect_answers": ["The Terminator Series", "The Bourne Series", "Indiana Jones Series"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the end of the 2006 movie The Break-Up, Gary and Brooke finally get back together.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "There is usually some bleeding during the process of tattooing.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How did Michael Moore finance his movie \u201eRoger and Me?\u201d", "correct_answer": "He ran bingo games.", "incorrect_answers": ["He sold hunting equipment.", "He sold over 100% of the film to investors", "He managed a Walmart in Flint, Michigan."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This Andean stratovolcano in Colombia erupted in 1993, killing 9 people.", "correct_answer": "Galeras", "incorrect_answers": ["Pasto", "Nina", "Paloma"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Quesadillas are folded tortillas, stuffed with cheese and then grilled.", "correct_answer": "Mexico", "incorrect_answers": ["China", "Italy", "Japan"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Wombats have an incredibly fast metabolism.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The study of unknown animals is known as Cryptozoology.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The African Bullfrog is the largest frog.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What Mediterranean island is divided between a Greek community and a Turkish community (although the latter is not internationally recognized as a separate entity)?", "correct_answer": "Cyprus", "incorrect_answers": ["Crete", "Corsica", "Malta"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In atomic physics what does the term magnetic moment refer to?", "correct_answer": "The magnetic field produced by an atom", "incorrect_answers": ["The moment in which an atom enters a magnetic field", "A miniature slice of time in an atoms magnetic interaction with other particles", "The moment in which an atom becomes magnetized"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The first novel of this Nobel Prize-winning author was called Lord of the Flies. The title is a literal English translation of one of the alternate names of the Devil -- Beelzebub.", "correct_answer": "William Golding", "incorrect_answers": ["J. R. R. Tolkien", "Peter Sinfield", "Steven Brust"]}]